[{"answer": "I'm doing well, Piers.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 28, "question": "Jesse, how are you?", "qSentId": 27}, {"answer": "You are looking very well.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 30, "question": "How re you?", "qSentId": 29}, {"answer": "Yes, that's true.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "I will.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "How does that work?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "We're already fascists, Piers.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "You're basically endorsing a form of fascism, aren't you?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "Well, I guess that -- here's what I thought when I read your book.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "Why is it just one way?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "Well, you can still -- you can turn the Democrats and Republicans into special interests, which is what they are anyway.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "How do you actually have a government that works if everyone is an independent?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "No, not necessarily.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "These would be independents formerly known as Democrats and Republicans, wouldn't they?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "Go on.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "You know why?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "You know why?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "Well, my reaction, it doesn't matter.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "When you hear the president and Republican nominee going at it like this, given the state of economy, what's your reaction?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "I think it's awful.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "I won't be boycotting them.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "So presumably you'll be boycotting FOX and MSNBC on your book tour, will you, Jesse?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "-- will have me on.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "Well, he is pulling them out.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "He has?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "Well, I guess he is.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "He's pulling them out, isn't he?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "Well, I'll give you a scenario.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "What would you do with Iran?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "You don't think --", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "So the U.S. -- the U.S. is definitely threatened by these countries in what way?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "Actually both were.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "You mean \"Dallas,\" not the royal wedding?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "More.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Was it all you hoped it would be when you signed up for this?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "We had this realization we would never work together again.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "Really, why?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "I mean, you look so nice and normal today.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "Were you remotely concerned, given that you were the top dog, if you like, that it might damage the brand?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "About until they told me how much I was going to make.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "How long did you think about it?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "I don't remember.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "How much was it?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "Well, I wouldn't be doing it without them.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "How much did the friendship come into it?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "So far, yeah.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "Is everything OK, back to normal?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "AGMAN: In Germany, it's not my chuckle.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "Was that your chuckle or was it one you perfected?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "He said that.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "Did you really say that?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "No wonder I drank.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "You think that's evil?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I don't think I was an evil man.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "Did you like being, for what you were for a long time, the most evil man on television?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "Especially against his own family.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "That is evil, isn't it?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "Of course I do, yes.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "Did you like the reputation?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "They -- the question they say is who shot J.R.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "How do people react even now?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "Yes, yeah.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "You ever tell them?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "Bing Crosby's daughter.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "What did you say?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "Everywhere.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "When you guys are filming in Dallas, presuming you live there for the duration, when you walk around, it must be like the royal family, isn't it?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "I think it was in the U.K.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "Where are you most popular outside America?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "Every night, yeah.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "Well, I actually was completely excited about what I considered to be a fun challenge.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "How do you feel about it?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "John Ross was a little baby.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "Is he everything like his father or nothing like his father?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "Am I right?", "qSentId": 627}, {"answer": "It's been wonderful.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 639, "question": "How have you found it coming into this iconic show?", "qSentId": 638}, {"answer": "I was born in 1980.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 645, "question": "How old were you when \"Dallas\" -- how old are you, if you don't mind me asking?", "qSentId": 644}, {"answer": "You know, I feel incredibly blessed to have the opportunity to be another television phenomenon.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "Jesse, for you, from \"Desperate House Wives\" to \"Dallas,\" does it get any better?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "They're going to drag us into another 13 years.", "docId": "120616pmt", "aSentId": 683, "question": "Can we have a little critique?", "qSentId": 682}]